<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<story>
  <cast>
    <group>Shields Family</group>
    <group>Capricorn Staff Core</group>
  </cast>
  <title>Family Reunion</title>

  <text>

    <abstract>
    The Shields Family goes to a family reunion/picnic accomponied by the Capricorn staff core. One of the paranormal investigators that Jindrich hired is at the picnic.
    Many characters come to realized that have more mutual connections as this story goes on. This is where several plot threads meet up. I need to make sure the events leading up to it have room to breath, and that this serves as a resolution.
    </abstract>
    <aside>Depending on where I place this in the timeline, May might have more attendents. Regardless, she'd probably be self consious enough to request a skeleton crew for this event, so only the core three will be there.</aside>
    <normal>May and her family have a yearly picnic with their extended family. Mr. Tannenbaum, Cacilius, and Noel come along.</normal>
    <aside>Before I get to this point- Establish a sign between Jindrich and May to indicate if someone knows about Zodiac magic, and if someone does not. In this event he'll give the sign that the relative does not know, but because I want other events to come to the forefront the sign should be given and understood smoothly.</aside>
    <normal>
      The three extra people get some attention, but don't seem too out of place until one of the realatives recongnizes Jindrich, "Mr. Tannenbaum?!"
      When May asks how they know each other, Jindrich responds, "I've hired her as a detective in the past."
      May glances at Jindrich, but he gives the sign she dosen't know about Zodiac magic. The relative picks up that they just comunicated something, but doesn't know what.
    </normal>
    <aside>
      Let's give this relative the working name of Jessica, as reference to Jessica Fletcher.
    </aside>
    <normal>When Jessica asks in turn why Mr.Tannenbaum is with the Shields family, Mr.Tannanbaum gives a business smile and says, "Mrs. May Shields is my current boss".
      Jessica takes a moment to register what he said and is then taken aback, "Come again? I thought you said that May was your boss, hahaha..."
      Jindrich nodds, with his business smile still in place, "No. You understood correctly. Mrs. May Shields is my boss."
      May looks a little embaressed, but nodds when Jessica looks at her for confirmation.
      Jessica takes a moment to process this, then wrinckles her brow, "I'd think you were pulling my leg if I didn't know that Mr.Tannenbaum never jokes."
    </normal>
    <aside>
      Like the signal, whatever working excuse they have should be down pat at this point.
      It'd make sense to have an episode before this where May dosen't quite get the excuse right and complications ensue.
    </aside>
    <normal>      May looked very tierd and says, "Technically that's true, but pragmatically he's my teacher right now. Mr. Tannanbaum's company was offering an accounting scholership with the possiblity of an internship, so I applied for it. Long story short, the scholership test they give is really close to the apptitude test used by the company Mr.Tannenbaum used to work for that would show potential for other parts of the business, and I scored very high on it. Mr.Tannenbaum contacted them about it, and further offered to tutor me. While it's not set in stone, if this goes well I could enter the company with Mr.Tannenbaum as my assistent."
    </normal>
    <aside>It feels wrong to introduce Jessica as a detective and then have her fall for a fake story hook, line, and sinker. As I refine this I'll have to consider what parts of the half truths May just said that she picks up on. She's also known May since she was a baby, so she's more likely to know May's tells. There's also the meta game here, where Jindrich might catch that Jessica caught something.
    </aside>
    <normal>As the explanation continued Jessica looked far less confused and grasped the situation more clearly. Mr.Tannenbaum waits for May to finish and then addresses Jessica, "There you have it. I'm also rather suprised to meet you here. I did background checks on both of you, due to the nature of our business agreements, but I didn't know you were related to each other."
      Jessica felt a shiver down her spine. Knowing Mr.Tannenbaum's information network, she woundered just how throughly she'd been investigated.
    </normal>



  </text>




</story>
