<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<story xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">

  <title>Twins Start In Festival</title>

<text>
    <abstract>
There exists a family of Pumpkin farmers with a lot of children. The oldest two are twins: a boy and a girl.
The twins enter a fashion compition at a festival in order to win some mushrooms.
In order to increase their changes of winning they enter as a pair, the boy reluctantly cross-dressing.
They run into a couple of witches who also entered the festival in order to win the mushrooms.
The witches reveal their identies, mistaking the twins for witches as well because of their Pumpkin motif and traces of magic in their outfits.
Once the mistake is realized, the witches have to backtrack quickly. They tell the twins that they have a natural talent for magic,
if they hand over the mushrooms they won in the contest and promise keep this whole magic thing a secret the witches will pull some strings
so they can attend a magic school for girls.
</abstract>
<draft>
The female twin is about to state that her brother isn't a girl, but he cuts her off because he dosen't want to risk not
getting in on the magic school shindig. The male twin phrases the question as more hypotetical, such as:
"Girl's school? Does that mean there's a seperate boy's school?"
The witch states,"Well, boys traditionally carry on whatever special magic runs in their family. I think I heard that
orginially the idea was that giving young witch a more rounded education would enable her to marry into other magic families more easily,
There are some special schools for boys too, but they're rare and pretty competative. I know there's a co-ed school in the West Virginia,
but to be completly frank their achademic program is pitiful."
</draft>
<aside>
Right now my thought is to set it up so the boy has to cross dress to attend the school,
but a forking path where he goes to the co-ed school might be interesting.
</aside>

</text>



<branch>
  <option>Follow Girl</option>
  <option xlink:type="simple"
  xlink:href="boyStartsAtGirlMagicSchool.xml">Follow Boy: Cross-dress and attend Girl's School</option>
  <option>Follow Boy: Go to co-ed School</option>
</branch>


</story>
